Guide to the Montana State University Extension Service Records 1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Administration, 1914-1970; 5
  - Supplement Administrative Files, 1966-1967 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Agricultural Planning Committee (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Banker-Farmer Program (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Contracts and Agreements; Farm Labor Programs (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - District Economic Conference, 1927-1938 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Drought Relief; Seed Loans, 1931 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Educational Work on AAA, 1938 September-December (Box 98, Folder 23-26)
  - Farm Security Administration, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - Farm Success Survey, 1922 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - Land Use Planning, 1939 (Box 98, Folder 29-30)
  - Montana Relief Commission, 1935 (Box 98, Folder 31-32)
  - National Defense Meetings, 1917 (Box 98, Folder 33)
  - Rural Rehabilitation and Resettlement; John Krall (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - County Agent Reports to Chancellor, 1916 (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - Young Adult Work; Correspondence, 1946 (Box 98, Folder 36)
  - Young Adult Work; Correspondence, 1947 (Box 98, Folder 37)
  - Young Adult Work; Older Youth Committee (Box 98, Folder 38)
  - Young Adult Work; Program Planning Bulletins (Box 98, Folder 39)
  - Young Adult Work; California (Box 98, Folder 40)
  - Young Adult Work; Colorado (Box 98, Folder 41)
  - Young Adult Work; Idaho (Box 98, Folder 42)
  - Young Adult Work; Minnesota (Box 98, Folder 43)
  - Young Adult Work; Nebraska (Box 98, Folder 44)
  - Young Adult Work; New York (Box 98, Folder 45)
  - Young Adult Work; Ohio (Box 98, Folder 46)
  - Young Adult Work; Oregon (Box 98, Folder 47)
  - Young Adult Work; University of Saskatchewan (Box 98, Folder 48)
  - Young Adult Work; Virginia (Box 98, Folder 49)
  - Young Adult Work; Washington (Box 98, Folder 50)
  - Young Adult Work; Wisconsin (Box 98, Folder 51)
  - Directives, 1967-1968 (Box 98, Folder 52)
  - Agricultural Production and Conservation; Arthur Shaw, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 53)
  - Agricultural Production and Conservation; Donald Luebbe, 1962-1966 (Box 98, Folder 54-57)
  - Agriculture and Economic Development; Donald Luebbe, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 58)
  - Community Development and Public Affairs; J. Glenn Jones, John Bower, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 59)
  - Community Development and Public Affairs; John Bower, 1962-1963 (Box 98, Folder 60-61)
  - Community and Resource Development; Don Hunter, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 62)
  - Extension Training; Harry Cosgriffe, 1957-1960 (Box 98, Folder 63-66)
  - Young Farm and Homemakers; J. C. Taylor, 1946 (Box 98, Folder 67)
- Microfilmed Records from the National Archives, 1914-1944; 6
  In 1952 the National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) decided to reduce the size of Record Group 33, Extension Service Records, by microfilming the annual reports submitted by agents in the various states, including Montana. These reports were, in most cases, carbon duplicates of the reports already on file at individual state offices and the offices of individual agents, but important exceptions remained. For example, sometimes photographs submitted with the report forwarded to Washington were not duplicated in the report retained at the state level. Also, additions to the annual reports held by the state and individual agents' offices occasionally were not sent to Washington and therefore not filmed. Since the potential for significant differences exists, the film has been retained as a separate series in this archives record group. NARA filmed the records in rough chronological order, with county agents, specialists, Indian agents, and administrative reports all mixed together by year. A comprehensive inventory of the microfilm reels, with a cross index, is included in Box 99.
  - 64 reels of microfilm and typed inventory (Box 99)